articlesisland.com 2010-11-21

# Privacy Policy - Articles island

This privacy statement created by [ArticlesIsland.com](http://www.articlesisland.com/) in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for ArticlesIsland.com.

 **IP**  
We use your IP address, browser type, domain names, and access times, operating system, country of origin, page views, and users sessions to help diagnose problems with our servers, and to administer our Web site. Your IP, etc. address is used to gather broad demographic information.

 **Cookies**  
Our Site uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart, and to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. We also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site.

 **Affiliated sites, linked sites and advertisements**  
ArticlesIsland.com expects its partners, advertisers and affiliates to respect the privacy of our users. Be aware, however, that third parties, including our partners, advertisers, affiliates and other content providers accessible through our site, may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices. For example, during your visit to our site you may link to, or view as part of a frame on a ArticlesIsland.com page, certain content that is actually created or hosted by a third party. Also, through ArticlesIsland.com you may be introduced to, or be able to access, information, Web sites, features, contests or sweepstakes offered by other parties. ArticlesIsland.com is not responsible for the actions or policies of such third parties. You should check the applicable privacy policies of those third parties when providing information on a feature or page operated by a third party.

While on our site, our advertisers, promotional partners or other third parties may use cookies or other technology to attempt to identify some of your preferences or retrieve information about you. For example, some of our advertising is served by third parties and may include cookies that enable the advertiser to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before. Other features available on our site may offer services operated by third parties and may use cookies or other technology to gather information. ArticlesIsland.com does not control the use of this technology by third parties or the resulting information, and is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties.

You should also be aware that if you voluntarily disclose Personally Identifiable Information on message boards or in chat areas, that information can be viewed publicly and can be collected and used by third parties without our knowledge and may result in unsolicited messages from other individuals or third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of ArticlesIsland.com and this policy.

 **Choice / OPT-IN**  
We provide opt-in opportunities for all email lists that you choose to receive. We use your email addresses to confirm your subscription and validity of the provided email address. Your reply to this email is necessary for completing your subscription to any email list.

 **Registration Forms**  
Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information like their name, email and etc.Contact information is used to send information about our company, and to send promotional material from some of our partners to our customers. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the customer when necessary. 

Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.

 **Choice/Opt-Out**  
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving promotional/marketing information from our partners, and us. You can send email to us: support@articlesisland.com

 **Surveys**  
The email addresses and contact information collected via publisher surveys are used solely to compile general statistical data. The users' personally identifiable information is never sold or given out to parties outside ArticlesIsland.com. All information is collected via the online form provided.

 **External Links**  
This site contains links to other sites. ArticlesIsland.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

 **Legal Disclaimer**  
Though we make every effort to preserve your privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal process served on our Web site.

 **Security**  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. These security measures include password protected directories through the use of .htaccess files and customized php script to prevent access to specific areas of the web site.

 **Subscription**  
ArticlesIsland.com uses subscription forms for individuals to request information by subscribing to Email Newsletters based on their categories of interest. We collect visitor's contact information (like your email address) to provide you with the information that you request. We will periodically send you email referring to news and updates to ArticlesIsland.com.  

 **Children**  
ArticlesIsland.com does not knowingly collect or solicit Personally Identifiable Information from or about children under 13 except as permitted by law. If we discover we have received any information from a child under 13 in violation of this policy, we will delete that information immediately.

 **Unsubscribe**  
We provide unsubscribe/opt-out opportunities for all email lists that you choose to receive. All email list welcome messages contain the information necessary for removal from the list.

 **Changes to this Policy**  
ArticlesIsland.com reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of our site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. Information collected prior to the time any change is posted will be used according to the rules and laws that applied at the time the information was collected.

 **Contacting the Web Site**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: Support@ArticlesIsland.com
